ellevatenetwork.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy | Ellevate

85 Broads Unlimited LLC dba Ellevate Network (“Ellevate”, “our”, “us” or “we”) provides this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to describe how we use and process certain information that we obtain through the web site at www.ellevatenetwork.com together with all sub-domains, extensions and pages (the “Site”). We invite all visitors to, or users of, the Site (“You”) to carefully review this Privacy Policy before continuing to access or use the Site.

We collect certain personally identifiable data that You submit through the Site (“Personal Data”) as well as other non-personally identifiable data that we collect through cookies and other tracking technologies (“Data”) in order for us to understand Your needs better and make Your experience at the Site more valuable to You. We may share this Personal Data and Data with our affiliates and use it consistent with this Privacy Policy. They may also combine it with other information to provide and improve our products, services, content, and advertising. You are not required to provide the Personal Data that we have requested, but, if You chose not to do so, in many cases we will not be able to provide You with our products or services or respond to any queries You may have.

You may sign up for membership, post articles, network with others or otherwise actively send us Personal Data using the Site. “Personal Data” includes, but is not limited to, Your name, email address(es), billing address(es), delivery address(es), telephone number(s), contact preferences and credit card information. Personal Data may also include Your education and work history and other skills and characteristics related to Your past, current or future occupational endeavors. You can amend or update Your Ellevate profile at any time and You can close such profile at any time. We use Personal Data primarily for the purpose for which You originally provided it (for example, to receive access to member events, to network with others, or the like), for purposes of improving our products and services and for market research. We may use Personal Data to transmit direct marketing communications to You by email.

This Site is not intended for use by persons under the age of thirteen. Individuals who are under the age of thirteen are expressly prohibited from submitting to Ellevate or posting to the Site any personally identifiable information about themselves.

When You visit the Site, we may passively collect Data through the use of cookies on Your computer and Internet connection, such as the IP address of Your computer and/or Internet service provider, the date and time You access the Site, the Internet address of websites from which You link to our Site, the computer technology You are using and Your movements and preferences on our Site. We may also use such cookies to collect information in connection with future visits to the Site (such as to remember Your user name and password), to recognize You as a previous visitor, and to track Your activity on the Site. We also reserve the right to use other technologies such as Internet tags, web beacons, and navigational Data collection tools to administer, protect, and improve our Site and our systems. We use this information for internal use only; we don't share it with others. If You choose to refuse to accept cookies, You may experience loss in Site functionality.

From time to time, we may contract with third parties to provide services on our behalf to maintain and add functionality to our Site, analyze data, provide marketing and customer assistance, and provide other services including, but not limited to, the ability to send, receive or view text, data and video messaging or communications. The Personal Data that we obtain through this Site may be accessed by these third parties as necessary to perform their functions, solely on our behalf, but we generally do not authorize these service providers to make any other use of Your Personal Data. By accepting to be bound by the Terms of Use You are consenting to our disclosure of such information to such third parties. We may also use data we have about You (such as the interests and preferences You have expressed) to determine whether You might be interested in career opportunities of a particular third party. We may also disclose Personal Data to financial institutions or other third parties in connection with performing payment transactions. We do not otherwise disclose Your Personal Data to third parties, unless such disclosure is required by law, necessary in connection with a legal claim or proceeding, necessary to protect the rights or interests of Ellevate or third parties, necessary to prevent a crime or protect national security, or necessary to protect the personal safety of users or the public. We cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who may be using our servers or services for illegal activities.

We reserve the right to disclose information submitted by or concerning any Member, as we reasonably believe is necessary to protect our systems or business. Specifically, but without limitation, we reserve the right to disclose such information when a Member is in violation of our Terms of Use or other published guidelines, or partakes (or is reasonably suspected of partaking) in any harmful, infringing or illegal activity, even without a subpoena, warrant, or other court order. We also reserve the right to report any suspected illegal activity to law enforcement for investigation or prosecution, or to suspend or terminate Your membership in connection with any suspected illegal or infringing activity.

If Ellevate is acquired by another entity or is merged or consolidated or subject to any other corporate transaction (collectively, “Corporate Transactions”), Personal Data may be made available to the prospective, acquiring, or resulting entity. However, in the event a Corporate Transaction occurs, Ellevate shall require such prospective or acquiring entity to protect the Personal Data in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

Members can be held liable for any illegal or prohibited User Content they provide to the Site or to other Members, including, for example, infringing, defamatory, or offensive materials. So that the Site is available for all users to enjoy, You may not, and hereby represent and warrant that You will not, post, transmit, email or otherwise make accessible on or through the Site User Content that:

(i) is unlawful, harmful, threatening, tortious, defamatory, libelous, abusive, disparaging, pedophilic, pornographic, obscene, invasive of another's privacy, hateful, or malicious;

(ii) contains hate propaganda or promotes discrimination or violence against any people on account of their race, national origin, religion, age, gender, disability, or sexual orientation;

(iii) is or could be harmful to minors;

(iv) harasses or advocates harassment of another person;

(v) involves the transmission of "junk mail," "chain letters," or unsolicited mass mailing (or "spamming");

(vi) promotes information that You know is false, misleading, or promotes illegal activities or conduct;

(vii) is or promotes an illegal or unauthorized copy of another person's work, such as providing pirated computer programs or links to them, or providing information to circumvent manufacture-installed copy-protect devices;

(viii) infringes any patent, copyright, trademark, service mark, trade secret, or other proprietary right of any other party;

(ix) contains restricted password only access pages, or hidden pages or images (those not linked to or from another accessible page);

(x) provides material that exploits people under the age of 18 in a sexual or violent manner, or solicits personal information from anyone under the age of 18;

(xi) provides instructional information about illegal activities such as making or buying illegal weapons, or providing or creating computer viruses;

(xii) contains a software virus or any other code files or programs that are designed to or have the ability to interrupt, destroy, compromise, or otherwise limit the functionality of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment whether owned by Ellevate or any other party;

(xiii) solicits passwords, or personal identifying information for commercial or unlawful purposes from other users; or

(xiv) otherwise violates any local, state, national or other applicable law or regulation.

In addition, You may not, in connection with Your use of the Site:

(i) impersonate any person or entity, including an Ellevate officer or employee, or falsely misrepresent Your organization_user with any other person or entity;

(ii) forge headers or otherwise manipulate identifiers for the purpose of disguising the origin of any User Content posted or transmitted through or on the Site;

(iii) engage in commercial activities and/or sales without Ellevate’s prior written consent including, without limitation, contests, sweepstakes, barter or advertising;

(iv) post or transmit any Content that You do not have the right to post or transmit;

(v) post or submit unsolicited commercial e-mail, chain letters, pyramid schemes, or seek or encourage others to engage in these activities;

(vi) disrupt the ordinary flow and operation of any portion of the Site, including causing a screen to scroll faster than another User may be able to type in a chat room or bulletin board environment;

(vii) interfere with or disrupt the Site or any server or network involved with the operation of the Site;

(viii) stalk or harass any other person; or

(ix) collect or "harvest" from the Site the names of other users for the purpose of transmitting to those other users unsolicited commercial messages.

If You discover this kind of material or activity on the Site, please contact [info@ellevatenetwork.com](mailto:info@ellevatenetwork.com). 

This Privacy Policy is effective as of June 3, 2014. This Privacy Policy is subject to the Terms of Use posted on the Site, including provisions regarding change or modification of this Privacy Policy and other policies as set forth in the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy. You are responsible for checking this page periodically for changes and updates to the Privacy Policy. If we make material changes, we will post a revised version of the Privacy Policy on the Site and notify You by indicating that the Privacy Policy has been revised. Your use of the Site following any posted changes to the Privacy Policy will be deemed an acceptance of such changes. This Privacy Policy is part of, and incorporated into the Terms of Use.

Please check back periodically, and especially before You provide any data to us. We will also indicate a revised Effective Date at the top of this Privacy Policy and the changes in the Privacy Policy will not be effective until thirty (30) days after first posting the revised version.

Please contact [info@ellevatenetwork.com](mailto:info@ellevatenetwork.com) with any comments or suggestions You might have regarding the information practices described in this Privacy Policy.
